question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the 'Shrek' film franchise, Donkey is played by Eddie Murphy.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the 1988 film 'Akira', Tetsuo ends up destroying Tokyo.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The card game 'Munchkin' won the 2001 Origins Award for Best Traditional Card Game.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Sonic the Hedgehog universe, Tails&#039; real name is Miles Prower.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "According to Greek Mythology, Atlas was an Olympian God.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Daft Punk originated in France.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "'27 Club' is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Chobits, Hideki found Chii in his apartment.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Rabbits can see what&#039;s behind themselves without turning their heads.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The game 'Jetpack Joyride' was created by 'Redbrick Studios'.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
